SUPER
SPECIAL
MOVE
Continuing from last time, I wanna come up with a
special attack that's good for a Shadow Mistress like me!
MR. SHIROSAWA'S SUPER MOVE
A super move? I hardly have
any combat power compared to humans.
But I do have a specialty.
My species is known for being exceptional
at fortune telling and prophecies.
Back in our home country,
we made our living by staying at the homes
of influential people and advising them on the future.
This path may lead you to a silver mine.
This path may lead you
to a silver mine
Whoa.
Whoa
Look up "Bai Ze" if you want to know more.
Fortune telling? Oh, do me!
I'm not as good now as I was in my prime,
but I can demonstrate for you.
You occasionally find yourself lacking confidence.
Wow! You're right!
You are regarded by others
as the type who can't say "no."
Wow! You're right!
Doesn't take much to impress you, huh, Shamiko?
LICO'S SUPER MOVE
I don't have any of those fancy-schmancy attacks,
but I do keep a little something up my sleeve
for dealing with priestesses.
Really? I wanna see it!
Um, well, I don't want to show you with Momo around.
I mean, there may be a time down the road
when it comes in handy...
Exactly what kind of scenario
are you imagining that it would?
Okay! I've got a real simple one
that I can show you here and now.
Momo, hun? Could you drink this for me?
I'm not drinking any liquid that's such a crazy color!
Yeah, that figures.
Momo, hun? Could you go clean up the glasses
that are left on the counter?
Not until you explain why there's something
that looks like a pitfall trap over there.
Doki doki wa kore kara!
Kiseki okoru yokan
Henachoko sajikagen de ii desho iza susume!
Ichika bachika yukeru donna basho datte
Motto kikasete core no oto made
Futari te o awasetara kowaku nai yo
Komatta toki ni wa
Omoidashite
Kimi ga iru tte koto
Onaji sora futari de miagete
Waraiatte tsurai koto mo norikoechaou
Dareka no tame ni ganbaru koto
Sore mo warukunai
Kyou mo tonari de
Tokimeki wa kore kara!
PITCH-BLACK FEELINGS!!
DARKNESS PEACH RETURNS!!
Morning Run
Snooze
Sleep
Morning Run
Snooze
Sleep
This morning, Momo Chiyoda
was feeling somewhat strange when she woke up.
Good morning. What's up with your voice today, Metako?
Crack!!
Huh? My glass just broke...
What the-?
A form that should still be fresh in your memories.
Yes, you know it and love it!
The dark side form of Magical Girl, Momo Chiyoda!
M-Momo, is everything okay?!
There was a big noise and flashy lights
that reached all the way to my room!
Shamiko...
Somehow I ended up going to the dark side again.
Huh?
But why...?
How?!
I don't know.
Also, I can't revert to my normal form.
Wha-? Wha-?! WHAAAAAAAAA?!
This is nuts!
TUMMY
Tummy... tummy... tummy...
So, hey, can I go ahead and rub your tummy?
TUMMY
You're gonna have to save that for later!
BANDA TERRACE
Oh dear. You don't seem very chipper today, boy.
Are you okay, physically?
Well, it doesn't hurt or make me feel tired.
But I'm unable to regulate the amount
of magic power being used to move my body.
See? I can't hold my strength back at all.
It's like my magic is constantly
discharging at max capacity.
That seems like something
even the regular Momo could do!
That seems
like something
even the regular
Momo could do!
At this rate, my magic will run out quickly
and I'll end up nothing but a core.
So, I need to revert back to normal ASAP.
It's so sad that we have to say goodbye to you, Momo!
You better make a bucketload
of doll vessels before you go!
I could grind your statue
into dust right now if I wanted to.
Right! I'll just be quiet over here.
YOSHIDA
Let's get going.
I may revert back like last time
if we have Mikan shoot me again.
I'll be honest, I wish I didn't have
to see you go through that over and over.
Does it bother you or something?
Huh? Well, yeah...
I understand that you all used some extreme measures
when Lady Momo gave herself to the darkness.
Swallowing strange elixirs
and forcibly changing her class.
That's likely what caused her core
to become so unstable.
It made me realize the way you went
to the dark side last time was just too reckless.
But I had to do something back then, because not
taking action would have made me feel like garbage.
I have no regrets about my decision.
So please don't let it bother you.
If you say so.
Let's stay calm and focus on doing what we can.
R-right.
On another note, what is up with that string?
Creep...
Honestly, I just wanna pull it!
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU PULL MOMO'S STRING?
Pop quiz. What happens if you pull Momo's string?
Number 1: Her skirt falls down.
Her skirt falls down.
Number 2: Her panties fall down.
Her panties fall down.
Number 3: Both her skirt and panties fall down.
Both her skirt and panties fall down.
Number 4: Sadly, it's only a decorative thing.
Sadly, it's only
a decorative thing.
Nothing falls down.
Twitch, twitch, twitch, twitch, twitch
Pardon me a moment!
Shamiko?!
I don't know what your deal is, but calm down.
I'm sorry!
Ding, ding, ding! The correct answer was this!
Did you get it right?
WHAT HAPPENS IF PULL MOMO'S STRING?
SHAMIKO GETS PUT INTO A HOLD
Anyways, let's do our best.
I know this is important, but you can't
just break down people's doors!
Well, it's impossible to adjust
how much strength I'm using!
Shudderrrr
What? So you might have totally obliterated me
with that move a minute ago...?
Wake up, Mikan!
Huh? Wuzzat? Why do you look like that?
I need you to strike my core
as hard as possible without killing me!
What?!
Oh gosh, I'm sorry! I'm so sorry about this!
We don't have time! Hurry and transform!
Then go outside! Move it, move it!
C'mon! Hurry it up! Chop chop! There's no time to waste!
What the heck is going on?!
BANDA TERRACE
What is the big deal?
This is SO not how I wanted to wake up!
BANDA TERRACE
Did it work?
Nope. I'm not reverting back.
Well, it wasn't me because I put my heart
into that shot and gave it everything that I had.
But you're so mean! How dare you wake me up like this!
Making me shoot an arrow at you!
Put yourself in my shoes, darn it!
It's the worst way to start the day!
My bad. I'm sorry... seriously.
Okay then, you're welcome!
It would be nice if you guys
could put yourself in my shoes, too.
Seeing as how I always get swept up in Mikan's curse...
How'd you get all the way up there, Ancestor?
Hey Shamiko, can you get in touch with Café Asura?
Sure.
Good gracious. That sounds like a real pickle!
Unfortunately, my medicine requires a teeny-weeny bit
of time to take full effect after you have a dose.
There's not much hope of it working
if things are already wonky.
Not to mention that keeping your qi in balance is really
only useful to help prevent bad things from happening.
Is that so...?
You sound down in the dumps.
D-don't worry! It would've been too late
even if you had taken my medicine the other day!
It's not your fault for refusing it!
You're good, so just pass into the afterlife
without any regrets!
Lico! Your attempt to reassure her
is only having the opposite effect!
Why don't you try asking Sion Ogura?
She may be able to offer a good solution.
I have her number on my phone in my room.
BUSTED!!!
Busteeeeeeed...
It's broken!
The screen is totally shattered!
Oh crap... that must have happened
when the alarm woke me up.
Now how do we contact her?
Faaaade...
M-Momo?! Is it just me or are you
becoming see-through somehow?!
This is bad. I'm almost out of magic!
Then we have to hurry and get a hold of Ogura!
Oh no... What to do? What to do?!
Looking for me?
Oh! It's Ogura!
I got the sense I was in big demand, so here I am!
But how did you know...?
Because I was listening on a tiny mic
that I installed in your demon god statue.
I had no idea she put that inside of me...
Also, I've been patrolling through your neighborhood
for 5 days a week just by coincidence.
Well, whatever! Thank you very much!
Oh, Shamiko. Despite the small misgivings you just had,
your gratefulness won out in the end, huh?
Thank you so much!
My interested was so piqued after everything that
happened last time that I've been researching non-stop
and waiting for an opportunity to help out!
That's nice, but stalking is a crim-! Mmph!
Do you know why I suddenly fell to the darkness?
This is just conjecture on my part,
but I think it was negative feelings you were having
that triggered the change.
Negative feelings?
Jealousy, paranoia, greed.
Any of the adverse type like that.
I've found many records throughout history
that describe people related to the Light Clan
who fell to the darkness all by themselves
after being overwhelmed with negative feelings.
Normally, it's not something that can happen so easily.
However, your core has been in an delicate position
Negative Gusts
Light
Core
Darkness
since that last incident,
Negative Gusts
Light
Core
Darkness
which made you very susceptible
to plummeting to the dark side!
That's a pretty elaborate diagram.
I get the feeling she saw this coming a mile away
and prepared for it ahead of time.
So, how can I change back?
As it stands, your core has slipped and switched over to
the dark class, which broke your link with the Light Clan.
All you need to do is make yourself happy again
by dealing with whatever negative feelings
you've been having lately.
That will reestablish your link with the Light Clan
and make it so you can return to normal! Maybe!
In other words...?
You gotta come totally clean and vent about
all the stuff that's been getting on your nerves lately!
All right, then I'm cool with just fading away like this.
No way! Don't you dare give up!
Momo! Please tell me what's been
making you so unhappy lately!
I have an idea of what caused it,
but I don't want to talk about it here!
Come on! What happened to all that
"let's do our best" stuff?!
You realize I'm gonna be a sobbing mess
if you disappear on us!
Nobody goes through life without
publicly embarrassing themselves once or twice!
Well, yesterday...
...after everything that happened, I wasn't able to relax
and enjoy the lunch Shamiko made.
Even though I did all my homework.
I had been really looking forward to it.
Momoaaaan....
THAT'S what drove you to the dark side?
The truth is I'm a very small-minded
and boring individual.
Gotta admit, that's kind of adorable.
Psheeeeew...
I just wanna drop off the face of the Earth right now.
Well, Momo is on the verge of a breakdown in more ways
than one, so let's hurry and feed her a lunch.
R-right!
What to make? What to make?
What to make?
But you know, it takes a lot of time to make a lunch.
Momo's magic might run dry while I'm still cooking!
Hold up, Shamiko.
You have one already! Just look in the fridge.
What do you think? How does it look?
Yeah, that's the one! The first lunch
that you worked really hard to make!
The dead leaf colored lunch!
No. I don't wanna serve her this!
There isn't time for anything else! Besides,
this is a lunch you made all on your own. Be proud of it!
Dead leaf colored...
I think it's a nice lunch that seems just like you.
What the heck does that mean?! Just shut up and eat it!
One problem. I can't hold my chopsticks.
Aw, jeez! Then open your mouth!
Ahhh....
Omelette!
Huff! Puff! Huff! Puff! Huff! Puff! Huff! Puff!
Is it good? Do you like it? Are you satisfied?
I'm back!
You did it!
Thanks, everybody.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
You'll need to be quick to regulate
any chaotic emotions that you have from now on.
Huh?
Well, you're going to remain susceptible
to slipping over to the dark side for some time.
And if it happens again,
I hope you'll let me come take more data!
What?!
So this is gonna keep happening?!
Don't give up, Momo! Learn to diffuse the mental bomb
you carry by staying tough and aware in life.
Momp-momp...
Momo looks down for the count.
Are you all right?
My core is exhausted.
I used up so much of my magic after
I unintentionally went back to the dark side.
But... it'll recover with time. I just need to take it easy.
There's a fix for that!
I know a place that will get Chiyoda
back on her feet! Lickity-split!
SLINK...
O-Ogura?!
And the name of that place is none other than:
Sakura Chiyoda's Secret Spring!
Great, but I'd like to know
why you came out of the ceiling first!
I mean, if you want to know why I'm in the attic,
then it's because there's an attic for me to be in!
How philosophic.
My sister has a secret spring?
I'd love to explain, but...
Shloop.
Slink.
I'm afraid that I can't get down because it's higher
than I thought, so could you help me with that first?
You didn't rehearse this?
I was too excited, so I didn't.
I'll make sure there's a ladder next time.
You're really planning to pop out from up above again?
Thanks for waiting!
Sakura Chiyoda's Secret Spring is a special place
where magical girls can rejuvenate themselves!
Very deep inside the mountainous region of Tama,
there is a mystical spring of water
that contains super-duper strong magic!
Apparently, it started as pure water that gushed out and
formed a puddle in the depths of an uninhabited cave.
But then a hole coincidentally opened up
in the ceiling of that cave and...
MOONLIGHT SHINED DOWN LIKE FLASH!
MAGIC WENT IN THE WATER LIKE ZAAAP!
NEGATIVE IONS FLEW IN LIKE KAWOOOOSH!
AND A NATURAL SPRING
OF MYTHICAL WATER WAS BOOOORN!
A miracle created through pure happenstance!
A TRUE WONDER OF NATURE!
Whoa there, you're all over the place.
All an injured magical girl has to do
is submerge themselves in that water
and their ether body will be healed!
How did you find out about such a wonderful place?
I read about it in the notes
that Chiyoda's big sister wrote!
Huh?
Oh, right. I left all the documents and notes
that belonged to my sister with Ogura.
I couldn't figure out what any of them said.
I'm working hard to decipher them all!
A healing spring sounds like something
straight out of a video game! I wanna go see it!
You've got some pretty dark stains on you, so you should
take a long soak. That will make them easy to get out!
Quit making me sound like dirty laundry
that needs to be washed.
I put the location data in a map app for you.
And while you're there, get some samples
of that water to bring back for me!
Mythical water is a fundamental ingredient in alchemy!
You're not going to come with us?
I'm an indoors person.
So hiking a mountain in summer would kill me.
I think it's probably more bearable
than being in a stuffy attic.
Thank you. We'll go check it out.
A mountain?
Sorry, I think I'm gonna have to pass on this one.
Why?!
I have to go to an interview
as part of my school transfer request.
TRANSFER APPROVED             STILL A STUDENT
And if I skip out on it, then I can't change schools!
Which means I'll lose my status as a student!
TRANSFER DENIED                      STUDENT
DEEP INNER TAMA STATION
Deep Inner Tama Station.
Hey, I've been here before.
Oh really?
Yeah, because I missed my stop.
So I guess the place we're going to
is private property that my sister owns.
It's out in the middle of nowhere, but it looks like
we can reach it by following the mountain trails.
There's a sign up ahead!
WARNING
This area is private property.
"This area is private property."
Because valuable resources can be found here,
many traps have been laid to help prevent theft
and also just because it's fun.
"Because valuable resources can be found here,
many traps have been laid to help prevent theft
and also just because it's fun."
...However
If you insist on entering,
then I hope you enjoy the difficulty of reaching the treasure!!
I know the only people who would bother coming out here
are my friends and family anyways!
-Chiyoda, the landlord
...however, if you insist on entering then I hope
you enjoy the difficulty of reaching the treasure!
I know the only people who would bother coming out
here are my friends and family anyways.
Chiyoda, the landlord.
What is she trying to say with this?
I'm not sure I get it either...
What kind of traps prevent thieves?
She probably used magic booby traps and familiars.
F-familiars?!
Many traps have been laid to help prevent
theft and also just because it's fun.
Considering my sister's personality, it's nothing deadly
and just stuff that'll comedically beat us up.
But I need you to fight since I'm too weak right now.
So what, you want me to walk into non-lethal traps
and get comedically beaten up?!
Yep, let's mov-
MOMOOOO!
La-dee-da, here I go!
This trap is safe even if somebody
totally ordinary stumbled upon it.
Aaah! A pitfall!
It's a pitfall expertly designed
SAFETY LADDER
TOTALLY OKAY
TO FALL IN!
SHOCK-ABSORBING CUSHIONS
EMERGENCY BUTTON
Presented by: The Safe Pitfall Committee
to meet with all compliance measures.
Oh, that wasn't so bad.
FULLY            TESTED
It was a just simple pitfall!
Where's the magic in that?!
Let's keep moving. This is a challenge from my sister.
I totally want to get my hands on that treasure!
You seem oddly motivated about this...
Well, I'm a little ticked off.
Shamiko. You walk in front.
That's cheating, darn it!
No, I'm giving us an equal opportunity to hit a pitfall.
Consider it part of your training.
New experiences are- hnrg!
MOMO!
Momo...!
It was cute hearing you go "hnrg."
She set traps that can trigger from behind, too?!
Momooooope...
Welp. Time to go home.
As if! Don't you dare give up!
I'm about to slip over to the dark side again.
Intruder. Intruder. Intruder.
In-in-in-intruder.
Go back. Go back. Go ba-ba-ba-ba-back.
Oh, now that's more like it!
Clench.
Clench
What the heck is that?
A wad of black licorice out for revenge?
It's a familiar that can operate on its own.
Gachunk! Gachunk! Gachunk! Gachunk!
Prepare for combat, Shadow Mistress!
Wah! I wasn't ready for this
to suddenly turn into a hardcore battle!
CRISIS MANAGEMENT FOOOORM!
Stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp, stomp.
It's been set at a pretty weak level.
Calm down! It's moving slower than you think!
Watching how your opponent moves is fighting 101!
Familiars have something similar to a core,
so aim for that!
I dunno what that looks like!
Please give me a hint!
A hint, huh?
You'd think the pink stone on its chest
would be obvious enough...
Just try thinking about it by yourself for a minute!
You're such a mean instructor!
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy.
Fidget, fidget... Fidget, fidget...
Hey! This thing can't climb up to high places!
So how about we just wait here until it gives up?
We can't navigate the mountain trail at night,
so you gotta hurry this up.
Um... er... it's weak point...
I can't find it! Oh, but I guess it doesn't matter
where it is if I just attack all over the place.
Okay, Whatchamacallit Rod!
Copy Mode: Mikan's Weapon!
Whoa!
I... I won!
I never figured out its weak point, but I still won!
W-well, I guess that worked out...
It looks like a cheap knock-off, but it copied
the abilities of the original pretty well.
It has such a weird construction.
Heh-heh!
It's so convenient!
IT'S SO CONVENIENT!
Yeah, that's for sure.
It's my first demonic victory! Yahoo! Yahoo!
THIS WAS THE WEAK POINT!
By the way, the pink stone
on its chest was the weak point.
That makes sense!
Hey, can I take this stone home with me?
I don't see why not. It belongs to my sister, anyway.
It's gonna be my treasure that I polish every day!
Ah! I also wanna take home some dirt
from the spot where I first claimed a victory.
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho!
Say, Momo? Could you snap a picture of me?
You realize you're not a baseball player, right?
THE DEMON GIRL CLAIMED HER SPOILS OF WAR
This is gonna be my treasure!
We finally made it...
So, this is Sakura Chiyoda's Secret Spring.
It's more of a waterfall, really...
Yep. Just a waterfall.
Are you going to skinny-dip, or did you bring a swimsuit?
Or maybe white training garbs? Or a loincloth?!
Will you quit being silly! I'm going in just like this!
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow!
Wow!
Seeing Momo get hit by this waterfall is so funny!
Can you stop with the bouncy tail, please?
How is it Momo? Do you feel any different?
I feel nothing.
I swear, the friendlier we get
the more of a nuisance you become!
Ka-splash...
Look! Your body has started glowing a little bit, Momo!
I'm feeling better somehow.
I guess this stuff must really work.
Think I could do this at home if we called a contractor
and had them take it all back in a tanker truck?
Hold on, I'm betting it wouldn't be as effective
without the leylines around here.
I thought standing under waterfalls
was supposed to cleanse wicked thoughts...
BANDA TERRACE
Amazing!
You brought back so much
of the mythical water for me, thanks!
It was really rough...
Care to explain why you're making a lab in my kitchen?
Because there's a kitchen for me to use!
What's that?
Oh!
This is a little prize that I picked up after winning a bat-
Oh! My! Gosh!
O-outstanding! Such a high-quality pink gem!
It's a super ultra power stone that's incredibly valuable!
You don't say?
It's even better than the mythical water!
But it's my treasur-
Thank you so much!
Huh?
This is the greatest souvenir of all time!
You two really are the best!
Oh joy! Oh joy!
Listen, it's actually my treasure that I won and...!
GRIND
Yes! I can make you the ultimate elixir with this!
GRIND          GRIND           GRIND           GRIND
Just you wait, Shamikooooooo!
My treasure...
Listen. It's okay because your beautiful memories
of that moment will live on in your heart forever.
You're not gonna get me to fall for that sappy crap!
Don't give up, Shamiko! At the very least,
display the dirt you got by putting it in a nice glass jar.
Now to have that girl pack up
and get out of my apartment.
Mata aeta ne drama nandatte? (howa howa)
Sugu (sugu!) oshie ni mo icchauzo (utou!)
Kakyuuteki naruhaya de (saa!)
Ara post mo "ohayou" nante (pikopiko)
Mou shippo made saeteru (waa!)
Hakusen o tondette itsu mentsudoeba
Kyou mo hajimatteku
Totsuzen ni mystery
Kurakura mayou kedo
Te to te o tori doko made mo susume
Guruguru machi wa mawari kagayaku
Korokoro toehatae shite
Yume o mazeta yoikagen wa
Kimi ni hana o sakaseru yo
Yomo made kakomu tetragon
Aa machikado ni hanataba
Nee ima wa mou sukoshi
Sottosotto sono hana o misete
Yokubacchaeba mou ikkai
PREVIEW
Momo! Is the power of Ms. Sakura's
spring working on you?
Yeah, there's a pleasant warmth
enveloping my whole body.
Shamiko, I need your help! But please don't scoop it up!
Huh?!
Now it's time for us to train your magic power, Shamiko!
THE ANCESTOR'S DOJO?! DEMONKIND'S ULTIMATE WEAPON
Hey, I know a good way to do that!