I wanna invent a good special attack
that's fit for a Shadow Mistress like me!
HOW THINGS USUALLY GO FOR SHAMIKO
SHE GETS INVOLVED IN SOMETHING
AND THEN ENDS UP BEING CHASED
I've been getting chased around a lot lately.
So I think having a super move to use
when I'm in trouble would be really awesome!
HOW THINGS USUALLY GO FOR SHAMIKO
SHE GETS INVOLVED IN SOMETHING
AND THEN ENDS UP BEING CHASED
Like, "Shadow Thingy!"
Or some cool-sounding name like that.
Forget about the name.
Start by figuring out something reliable that you
can attack your opponents with in an emergency.
Like beams, or punches, or a deathlock.
We're talking about when I'm in the dreamscape, right?
Just think about what you can do in reality for now.
Plip plop. Plip plop. Plip plop. Plip plop.
Then the only thing I can reliably attack with are tears.
Okay, so I guess your super move will be
"Shadow Weepy Tears."
The stress of dealing with an emergency situation
will prevent you from using your full strength.
Not to mention that you need different strategies
to get out of different situations.
So let's do some practice!
Grip.
GRIP
Uh oh. I don't like the sound of that.
Okay, situation 1: when someone grabs you
by the collar, do this!
Huh?
Blargh!
Situation 2: when you need to incapacitate
someone who's resisting, do this!
Whoa, mind if I snap some pics?
Click
Bwlarghef!
I can't stop my Shadow Weepy Tears from coming out.
Click
Well, now you've gained some experience,
but you can't use any of the techniques
I just showed you because
your opponents typically won't use martial arts to attack.
Go ahead and forget it all.
Curse you!
The excitement has just begun!
I have a feeling that a miracle will occur
A novice's skill is enough. Now, let's go!
It's all or nothing. We can go anywhere
Let me hear more even the sound of the core
If you and I put our hands together, there is nothing to fear
When I'm at a loss what to do,
I'll remember that you are here for me
You and I look up at the same sky
We smile at each other and overcome hardship, too
Doing our best for someone
Isn't bad, too,
We are side by side again today
The excitement has just begun
SPARKS FLY?!
LIGHT AND DARK GO ON A JOINT EXCURSION!
I made plans to visit the zoo with Momo and Mikan.
I wanna eat a lunch that you
spared no effort to make for me.
This is my big chance to show
just how dependable a Demon Girl can be!
I'm gonna make the greatest
and most sublime lunch in existence!
I'll do a practice run using
the ingredients we have in the house first.
SOME
HOURS
LATER
What do you think? How does it look?
Who are you talking to, Shamiko?
I think it's boring since the colors don't pop.
If we're going out for a picnic,
then I want it to have more glitz and glam.
I think the darker tones look nice.
Fitting for a demon, anyway.
But I need to take the magical girls by surprise
by making something that packs a punch!
Okay, try covering the whole thing
with seaweed to make ipackt pitch-black,
then adding a healthy splash of ketchup
right in the middle!
CURSED
Demonic Lunch, garnished with gore.
DEMONIC LUNCH
~GARNISHED WITH GORE~
That's not the kind of surprise I meant!
Aw, poo...
Gosh, Shamiko, the color of this lunch you made
reminds me of dead leaves...
I think I'm going to retract my offer
to become your vassal.
Whaaaaaaat?!
I just don't have enough experience making lunches.
This calls for a different approach!
I'll go ahead and put this lunch
that you made in the fridge, then.
The dead leaf coloring makes it seem extra appetizing!
CAFÉ
ASURA
You want help making a box lunch?
Yeah.
Can you teach me how to make a lunch
that would leave a magical girl drooling?
I figured you two might know since you sold
those fancy box lunches the other day.
Ah, you mean the ones
from the shopping district festival?
We've got box lunches for sale! Buy tasty box lunches here!
Yes, those ones!
Well, that tickles me pink! I'll gladly teach you, hun!
Alrighty, the first step to a good lunch
is picking your ingredients.
Are those leaves?
From the right: one that paralyzes, one that causes
drowsiness, and one that heats the body up.
Um, just so we're clear, I'm not trying to drug anybody!
LEAF THAT
HEATS THE BODY
CAUSES DROWSINESS
LEAF THAT
PARALYZES
100% ORGANIC
Ain't nothing to worry about, they're totally organic!
So, you wanna make a colorful lunch, huh?
Personally, I think a brown shade is just fine.
Because what matters most
are the vibes that you put into it.
What do you mean?
Just picture your friends happily chowing down
on your food and then let your hands do the work.
Is it just me or are your hands glowing?!
Is everything okay?!
Here. For you, bossman!
Uh, no thanks.
Eat up!
This tasty morsel is filled with my positive vibes...
Can't you see?
Eat up!
Amazing, Lico. There are so many rainbow leaves
flying through the air right now...
Ain't it just wonderful?
That's a big nope! Please teach me something else!
GLOWING RICEBALL
RICE:     A GOOD AMOUNT
SALT:          TO TASTE
MAKES YOU HALLUCINATE
RAINBOW LEAVES
SEAWEED:      DAMP
VIBES:         PLENTIFUL
*Effectiveness will vary by person
Your taste buds won't believe how
mind-blowingly delicious these Huli jing riceballs are!
Absolutely not available for purchase!
It's chow time!
Listen, Yuko.
You gotta make sure that the flavors and colors
of your side dishes don't overlap.
Separate 'em like: sweet, sour, and salty.
Uh-huh. I got it.
Then for colors: red, yellow, green, black, and white are
the best ones to use to make something look really tasty.
Rainbow cellophane! Marmalade sky! I am the egg man.
C'mon, let's give it a try!
You know how to make just about anything, huh, Lico?
Well, I've spent a long time moseying
from one place to the next.
So I learned how to make food from all over the world.
Which is nice and all, but no matter where I seem to go...
...for some cockamamie reason I always end up
getting chased around and then forced to quit.
Come now, Lico! The reason for that should be obvious!
It's because you do crazy things like
giving your employer psychedelic hallucinations!
Aw. But I just wanted to show you something pretty,
since I adore you so much, boss.
You're forgiven.
So he's okay with it...
There were also a lot of times
when I had to quit after a priestess found me.
I took an interest in cooking pretty much right after
I became able to disguise myself as human.
Soy Sauce
I snuck my way into a number of kitchens
and always cooked dishes with great love and care.
Mirin
Sake
Garlic
Ginger
But back when I was a cub, I would put
a teeny-weeny bit too many positive vibes in my food.
Salt
Pepper
CLOSED
Give us food!
Give us food! Give us food! Give us food! Give us food!
Which sorta caused a teeny-weeny problem
with crowds banging at the doors.
Give us food!
That sounds like more than a teeny-weeny problem!
So, I kept having to move around after the local priestess
caught on to me and eventually ended up here.
Sounds like an ordeal.
Now I know better.
The best kind of smile that my food can put
on a customer's face is a completely natural one.
Being able to cook in this city
without any fuss is like a dream come true.
And it's all thanks to Lady Sakura
and the bossman here for taking me in.
Aw, Lico...
I get to eat three meals and nap on the job, plus I don't
have to come out of my den when I don't feel like it,
and lately I haven't had to interact
with the customers at all.
It's Heaven.
Uh, Lico?
Marinate for 20 Minutes
Anyhoo, it seems like most priestesses
don't care two hoots about us these days.
But you should still be careful out there, hun.
You know, not every Magical Girl out there
is the easy-going type like I am!
I want you to protect them and yourself.
What even are Magical Girls, anyway?
Who asked them to fight in the first place?
Do they get some kind of reward for defeating demons?
Magical Girls are ordinary humans who fight after
they forge a pact with beings from the Light Clan.
Or so I hear.
The time hath come!
FAMILIARS OF THE LIGHT CLAN
From what I understand, the girls who get contracted
Wassup?!
are chosen by familiars of the light clan that have
possessed animal bodies.
Gulp...
And who exactly is the "Light Clan"?
I have no idea.
I got no clue.
We haven't had much of an opportunity for peaceful talks
with anybody from the magical girl side, you know.
You should ask Lady Momo if you want to learn more.
HAMMER
But in terms of a reward, I know that whenever a magical
girl succeeds in weakening and incapacitating us,
they receive some sort of
"vanquishment token" from their familiar.
And it seems they are rewarded
after collecting a number of those.
A token...
The more of those tokens that they collect,
the grander the wish they can have granted.
They get a wish granted?!
That sounds like a really good deal!
You said it. In a matter of speaking,
we're like a walking jackpot to them.
But the majority of magical girls these days are friendly.
You'll be fine as long as you avoid doing anything
to disrupt the peace in the neighborhood.
Hopefully.
Despite how much they'd gain from defeating me,
Momo and Mikan have been protecting me instead...
VICIOUS MIKAN
Nothing in my wardrobe is suitable for a picnic...
But I feel pretty weird wearing yours.
Momowampus...
Given your physique, I think you'd be better off
wearing a simple, black t-shirt or something.
O-oh my gosh, I'm gonna have to make
an ultra yummy lunch to try and return the favor!
It has to be something to put a smile on their faces!
That's the spirit!
Use this mushroom that'll make it
so they can't stop laughing!
No way, José!
The meat's all seasoned, so let's get to cookin'.
We've only got one wok that's prepped for use right now,
so I'll show you how it's done.
Oh, that's not a problem. I think I can make another wok!
Say what?
Well, there's this rod that I inherited from my father.
And I can transform it into pretty much anything!
This is a perfectly seasoned and refined wok...
It's got a film of oil covering the whole thing.
What on Earth? Nothing should be able to transform like
that without totally disregarding the laws of nature!
I don't really get how it works, but it sure is convenient.
That seems like a huge understatement
considering what it can do!
It's a lifesaver whenever I forget to bring a pen!
So, it can just transform without any restrictions?
As long as it's something I can imagine
as being stick-like in my head,
then it can become pretty much whatever I want.
Will you let me have it?
Uh, I don't think so...
Lico, dear, you really need to fix
those bad habits of yours.
You can dive into people's dreams, right?
Pretty much anybody who's asleep, yeah.
I hope you don't feel your talents are wasted working
in this podunk café. You're not going to quit on us, right?!
Uh, yeah. I'd very much like to keep working here.
You know, there is a good possibility...
...that you could save a lot of people
if you put your mind to it.
Huh?
However, for her to have so much raw potential
at such a young age
means that her powers could mature considerably
in either a good way or a bad way as she gets older.
I just hope that no callous magical girls
set their sights on her.
Focus, hun.
The fried chicken was burnt black in an instant!
It's because you let the oil get too hot.
I guess even your almighty rod
still needs temperature control.
I'm sure the potential is there, but... yeah.
YOU CAN CALL
YOURSELF A PRO!
WOK PRE-SEASONED WITH OIL
The oil film that coats this pan has been carefully
produced to mimic those belonging to master chefs!
Enjoy the pleasure of being a pro in your very own home!
SIMPLE
BLACK T-SHIRT
Mikan gave me all that advice about clothes, but...
I honestly don't get it.
SIMPLE                 SIMPLE
BLACK T-SHIRT      WHITE T-SHIRT
What does she mean by "a simple black t-shirt"?
SIMPLE BLACK T-SHIRT
Heck yeah!
Excuse me! Can I get this in an L size?
Don't give up, Magical Girl! Get through the summer
with a simple and coordinated wardrobe.
Very simple!
SIMPLE BLACK T-SHIRT
My sample side dishes are finished!
Good on ya!
I know! Why don't you use the lacquer lunch
boxes we have in the shop?
You went through so much to cook that lunch,
you might as well make it look extra pretty!
Wow, thank you!
Except there's one little problem.
This box was made to fit enough food for 4 or 5 people.
This picnic is just for you and 2 magical girls, right?
You're gonna end up with some leftovers.
UHHHHH...
Here's an idea!
THE NEXT DAY
THE PARK WHERE YOU CAN FIND LOTS OF CATS
There are so many cats here!
Yeah, this is the park where you can find lots of cats.
So, you settled on wearing that outfit, huh?
There was a black t-shirt that seemed perfect for me.
But they didn't have it in my size.
Thanks for letting me borrow these.
You're welcome! But c'mon, why so grumpy?
I don't mean to sound ungrateful,
but I just don't think this is a good look for me.
Momo! Mikan! Good morning!
Shamiko!
Hey, Momo! Nice to see you!
Uh, yeah, hello there...
What?
You're heavy!
I am so sorry.
I was utterly powerless to stop Lico.
I've never been to a zoo before!
Let's all have a good time!
Oh wow!
You're looking cuter than a button today, hun!
Why? What's the occasion?
Uh, right. But I'm going to get changed now.
Don't give up, Shamiko!
The day for your get-together at the zoo has come!
Tama Zoological Park
Tama Zoological Park!
Now it's time for an exciting trip to the zoo!
Let's have a blast today, you guys!
All of us? Are you sure it's okay that we tag along?
Ticket
Of course! It says up to 5 people
can get in with this ticket.
SHUDDER
It's not the number of us that I'm worried about, Yuko!
Let's just say... it feels like an immense pressure
from nearby is about to squish me flat!
What did you come for?
Today was supposed to be a fun day at the zoo.
If you must know, we came here to help you
out of the goodness of our hearts.
Shucks, Momo. It hurts to see you
get so steamed up about this.
You even ditched that cute outfit you were wearing.
THE DAM IN MOMO'S HEART
Cut to the chase.
Translation: Please explain yourself quickly
before the dam in my heart gets full enough to burst.
Please explain yourself quickly
Well, we heard that you like animals!
And guess what? We're cute animals, too!
So, we figured that tagging along with you
would make today even more fun!
AIN'T I
Ain't I generous?
GENEROUS?
How about that.
Translation: I get the feeling I won't be able to make
any sense of this, so I'm going to quit asking.
I get the feeling I won't be able to make
Don't be silly, Lico.
You know that we came here for something
far more important. The magical girl here needs...
Yargh!
Boss!
My back is still on the mend...
Ahaha!
My apologies for being so fragile.
Just leave me behind and go enjoy the zoo...
Sounds good.
We'll just have Lico take you back home right now.
We can't do that!
Let me carry your bags!
Huh? You're letting them stay?
This is supposed to be a group outing!
Pain, pain, go away!
PAIN
Whoa! Something did fly away!
Are you all right?
Chill~ Chill~
Chill~
I'm feeling better.
The cooling pad is working, so thank you.
Benefits to Being a Bipedal Creature
-Can hold tools
-Can support a large brain
My species is actually quadrupedal by nature, you see.
So I often suffer from back pain
because I force myself to stand on two legs instead.
Oh no, that's awful!
It's a living hell. But, that being said...
I have no other choice but to walk on two legs
if I want to keep a low profile when living among humans.
I imagine that a tapir walking on two legs would actually
draw a ridiculous amount of attention to itself,
but let's not sweat the small stuff.
That's rough
That's rough.
I'm glad you made it back on your feet.
Thank you. Sorry for the trouble.
Momo!
Are you sure you didn't just want to do this
alone with Shamiko?
Huh?
No! I think going with a big group
is the best way to enjoy the zoo!
But the problem is I basically assaulted
their café the first time we met,
and I get the impression that Lico
doesn't enjoy my company very much.
That couldn't be further from the truth, hun!
You're a little cutie-patootie in my eyes!
Huh?
She's got an acute sense of hearing!
Several times stronger than any human!
THE MOUSE HOUSE
Anyhoo, let's go enjoy ourselves!
We brought a really big lunch, so everybody's
gotta get in some steps to empty their bellies!
Okay!
Did you know that baby Malayan tapirs
have a very intricate camouflage on their fur?
Wow, you're right!
They look totally different from the adults!
So, are the itty-bitty animals your favorite?
I guess.
Same here!
They cook real fast, which makes 'em good
boiled, baked, or even fried.
I don't think we're on the same page here.
Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe! Giraffe!
You can tell that its summer vacation
from all the big crowds out today!
Yeah.
What's that group over there looking at?
Huh?
Boss?!
Oh, I'm not part of the petting zoo area.
But you're still welcome to pet me.
This tapir is so adorable!
Wait. I think I remember this tapir from somewhere...
Oh, you're a regular at the café.
It's me! The owner of Asura.
I wanna pet it!
DOG
STAYING AT HOME FOR TODAY
We'll go for a nice walk once I get back. Okay, boy?
We offer pictures for 1,800 yen, folks!
I wanna pet it!
Stop, Lico! None of your greedy little schemes!
We heard one of the tapirs escaped!
Oh, I'm just a tapir visiting from abroad.
A tapir visiting a zoo...
Well, guess we don't have to catch a tapir
that's from somewhere else.
THE OWNER OF CAFÉ ASURA: SHIROSAWA
I'm a good guy tapir!
I'm so sorry for budging in on your girls' day out...
It's no problem.
Oh, that reminds me.
What was the important thing
you were trying to explain earlier?
Don't be silly, Lico. You know that we came here
for something far more important.
The magical girl here needs... yargh!
Ah, of course.
We animals have more sensory organs
than you humans do,
so sometimes we pick up
on strange things that you can't.
And for that reason, there's something
concerning us about Lady Momo...
What is it?
Momo!
I've been looking all over for you!
Sorry. I got so distracted by the view here
that I fell behind.
Are the others waiting for us?
Actually...
Everybody ended up having to go home all of a sudden.
Huh?
I gotta go home and water my potted mikan plants.
Uh oh! I think I left the heat on the tempura oil!
Ugh! I'm having one of my chronic fits of drowsiness!
So...
What the heck?
And after all the trouble
I went through to make this big lunch!
I hope they didn't leave for my sake...
I'm sorry. Our fun little picnic
turned into such a huge mess.
Oh, that's okay. To be honest,
I was kind of enjoying all the craziness.
I'm glad to hear that.
This seems like a good time for a break. Let's eat!
Okay.
SAKURA PLAZA
A GREAT PLACE FOR A PICNIC
So, hey, I really want to get closer with you.
I'm glad we made the time to hang out.
Now we finally have a chance to just talk.
So, why did you become a magical girl, Momo?
PRESS
What do you want to be in the future?
What's your weakness? Are there any foods you hate?!
PRESS
That's a pretty intense barrage of questions...
You know... I really love this city!
And since we're working together to protect it,
I want to know all about you!
I feel exactly the same.
But...
GRIP
Huh?
Using dirty tricks like this... is a big no-no!
Fresh Peach Outer Reap!
Aw, phooey!
Why couldn't you just play along?
I knew you'd pull something like this, Lico!
So, I take it that you were trying to trick me
into eating these leaves, huh?
How'd you figure it out?
Your tone, gestures, level of eye contact, rhythm of
breath, tail movement, excess core strength, and so on.
All of it was way off!
Whoa... you can't be for real...
And most importantly...
...there's no way Shamiko could ever be
that straightforward with me.
Now I get it. That's really good to know.
Lico! Lady Momo! Where have you been?!
I blew it, boss! The switcheroo was a big failure!
GROVEEEEL!
I'm so sorry, I should have known better
than to let Lico out of my sight!
Wow! It's a tapir!
P-please pick yourself up. There are children watching.
If you want Lady Momo to take a dose of your medicine,
then you need to be upfront and ask her!
Medicine?
Well, it's about your magic power.
It's been a teeny-bit unstable recently.
That's why I wanted you
to eat some of my medicinal cuisine.
It's really effective in curing unstable qi!
These raw leaves are "medicinal cuisine"...?
I thought you might enjoy chowing down
on it more if I tricked you into it.
I understand that you all used some extreme measures
when Lady Momo gave herself to the darkness.
Swallowing strange elixirs
and forcibly changing her class.
That's likely what caused her core
to become so unstable.
It's bad for your body and mind
if you let your qi stay bent out of shape like that.
But we knew you'd be too suspicious to trust us.
Let me get this straight, you put on this whole ruse
just to try and get me to take medicine?
Lico is kind at heart and generally acts in good faith.
But I also did it partly because watching
a priestess chew on grass that I tricked her into eating
You need to shut up, Lico.
F-forget about that and let's all
patch things up over a nice lunch!
I cooked a ton of stuff.
COLD
GLASS / CANS           PLASTICS
Despite all the trickery, I was being honest
when I said that I want to get closer with you.
Well, I don't have a problem taking medicine,
so long as you explain the situation to me first.
Really?
Boy, I didn't think a baby tiger could be that fluffy!
Being able to pet something with fur
that silky soft must come only once in a lifetime!
Yeah, you said it!
Once in a lifetime...?
Okay! Here's 800 of 'em to eat before lunch!
I guess we're just never going to be on the same page.
But you said you would take the medicine!
I have my limits!
The whole reason I came here was to eat LUNCH!
No fighting!
Speaking of which, Momo...
You haven't forgotten about
the other reason you came today, right?
SHOCK...
Your special chance to hug a baby tiger
that came with our VIP tickets...
THE VIP
PETTING ZOO AREA
CLOSED AT 2 PM TODAY
I totally forgot...
Have I mentioned how fluffy I am in my fox form?
You can hug me if you want.
SNAP
No thank you!
Don't think this means you've won...
Don't think this means you've won....
Momo! I wanna hug her next!
Fluffy...
Momo! I also wanna have a turn after that!
Don't give up, Shamiko! Gather around the dining table
and let bygones be bygones.
Lico was so soft to the touch!
I hope we can hug her again.
Seems like everybody enjoyed their day out at the zoo.
Now then...
I think it's about time for me
to start having some fun of my own...
Bwa? Wuzzat...?
What have I been doing all this time?
Was I asleep? Have I been sleeping?
I think Shamiko said they were going
to visit the zoo or something...
But nobody's tried to talk with me at all today...
Shamiko? Momo? Mikan?
I really wanted to have more dialog...
TO BE CONTINUED
Hey guys, it's Anri! I managed to finish
all of my summer homework!
We met again. It's drama?
I'll go tell someone at once
As soon as possible
Oh, even the post box says "Good morning"
Even my tail is sharp
If our usual members gather and jump over the white lines
Today will start, too
A sudden mystery
Makes me feel dizzy and at a loss
But we will hold hands and go anywhere we want
The city is turning and shining
Around and around many times
The night mixed with dreams
Will make you blossom
The tetragon that surrounds four sides
Ah, a bouquet for our neighborhood
Hey, now, just a little bit more
Show me the flowers secretly
Once more if I get greedy!
PREVIEW
Time sure flies when you're having fun with friends, huh?
I still refuse to accept this.
What's bothering you, Momo?
Shamiko! Did you need me? Here I am!
I know a whole bunch of stuff that could be helpful!
PITCH-BLACK FEELINGS!! DARKNESS PEACH RETURNS!!
In fact, here's something interesting about Chiyoda...
Ogura! This isn't the place to advance the plot!